{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Energy Auditors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46421/":{"taskOID":46421,"originalTaskOID":46421,"setID":1406,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6890,"questionDisplayText":"Primary Motivation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is your primary motivation for getting a home energy audit? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","answerDisplayText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Utility bill savings","answerDisplayText":"Utility bill savings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Inspection","answerDisplayText":"Home Inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500603,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of home:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"Square footage of home:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204432,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2,000","answerDisplayText":"More than 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6911,"questionDisplayText":"How old is your home (in years)?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your home (in years)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9990,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9991,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"21- 30 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9992,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"31- 40 years","answerDisplayText":"31 - 40 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9993,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"41- 50 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9994,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"More than 50 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 50 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9995,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6891,"questionDisplayText":"Please select any primary areas of concern: (Select all that apply)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select any primary areas of concern: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","answerDisplayText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9882,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9883,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic space","answerDisplayText":"Attic space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9884,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Appliances or Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Appliances or Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6890,"questionDisplayText":"Primary Motivation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is your primary motivation for getting a home energy audit? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","answerDisplayText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Utility bill savings","answerDisplayText":"Utility bill savings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Inspection","answerDisplayText":"Home Inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","answerDisplayText":"Environmental (Reducing greenhouse gasses)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Utility bill savings","answerDisplayText":"Utility bill savings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Inspection","answerDisplayText":"Home Inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500603,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of home:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"Square footage of home:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204432,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2,000","answerDisplayText":"More than 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204432,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2,000","answerDisplayText":"More than 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6911,"questionDisplayText":"How old is your home (in years)?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your home (in years)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9990,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9991,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"21- 30 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9992,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"31- 40 years","answerDisplayText":"31 - 40 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9993,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"41- 50 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9994,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"More than 50 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 50 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9995,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9990,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9991,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"21- 30 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9992,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"31- 40 years","answerDisplayText":"31 - 40 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9993,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"41- 50 years","answerDisplayText":"21 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9994,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"More than 50 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 50 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9995,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6891,"questionDisplayText":"Please select any primary areas of concern: (Select all that apply)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select any primary areas of concern: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","answerDisplayText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9882,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9883,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic space","answerDisplayText":"Attic space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9884,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Appliances or Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Appliances or Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","answerDisplayText":"Furnace or Air conditioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","answerDisplayText":"Windows \u0026 Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9882,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9883,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic space","answerDisplayText":"Attic space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9884,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Appliances or Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Appliances or Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46421/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46421,"taskName":"Home Energy Audit","taskDescription":"Home Energy Audit","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Energy Auditors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":121,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"energy audits","textMessagingName":"Home Energy Audit","rolloverLongDesc":"Determines the energy efficiency of a home by inspecting heating, AC, ducts, windows, insulation and appliances.","rolloverShortDesc":"Typically done to reduce energy usage and lower utility bills","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to perform a home energy audit. HomeAdvisor will connect you with local, prescreened, and customer-rated home energy auditors.","htmlTitle":"Home Energy Audit \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Home Energy Auditors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":42,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Home Energy Audit","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Energy Audit","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Energy Audit Need","urlName":"Home-Energy-Audit","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Energy Audit Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"energy,audits","emcCategoryOid":-12041,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1406,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}